<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KR Dvorak</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://http://kreighza.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://http://kreighza.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 04:26:22 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 04:26:22 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starstrand City</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog-posts/post1/cover.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Starstrand City: Downtown&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new DLC of Cities Skylines just came out and I am extremely happy that
somebody gave it to me as a gift! I’ve been playing this game ever since it first came
out and I even bought the other DLC. I think this DLC is so freaking cool! Snow and trams
have been in my wish list ever since I saw them on SimCity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city I’m building right now is
called Starstrand. It’s a city with a population of 30,000 people all crammed
into this one tiny island. My city planning skills are abysmal at the moment but I’ve been
trying to look up real world cities and interchanges. I think I’m getting there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog-posts/post1/screenshot1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A Ski Resort (Is that how westerners call it?) right at the edge of the hustle and bustle.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I built a ski resort right next to the train station in the city center. I was trying to attract more
tourists, but I think it would be better if I move it somewhere more remote. I could build a hill or
a mountain and then place winding dirt roads towards the entrance. It sounds cliche, but if
I were a tourist who would go to these kind of places, I wouldn’t want to hear the
honk of a dozen lorries delivering stuff to a nearby commercial building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog-posts/post1/screenshot2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Traffic is building up as the sun comes down.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then, there’s the coast line. I really like tracing coastlines, I think they look cool and very
realistic. I have added trams on the two lane road so that more cims get forced to see
the river as they commute to school or work. It’s not much of a view, but it’s something.
I plan to add a small dock where cims can go fishing or something, but unfortunately the water
is too far from the road, which makes plopping of assets a pain the ass. I’ll probably have
to terraform this thing - something I’m not very confident about, considering that there’s no undo
button in this game!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 13:04:40 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://http://kreighza.github.io/cities%20skylines/2016/02/25/post1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://http://kreighza.github.io/cities%20skylines/2016/02/25/post1.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>cities skylines</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
